{
    "id": "0ae0ea0601ea40a7bba5b4b5acba8a24",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Speak",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "When I said work hours should be reduced I was speaking ............................. all employees.",
            "description": "To speak for is to speak on somebody's behalf.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e83d468420a1426aa48f96e47124595b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The restaurant gets really crowded in the evenings. Be sure to speak ................................... a table.",
            "description": "To speak for a table is to reserve it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1ea2e595aea0448baad1185f036b1100"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a fabulous writer. Her stories speak ................................... themselves.",
            "description": "When a story speaks for itself, it represents a certain quality.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f48c7427d5b44e02bcbe3093f257ae54"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am speaking ................................ myself, not for my colleagues.",
            "description": "To speak for yourself is to speak on your behalf.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06a82f9ff0d54c3b85e338ae49a71d22"
        },
        {
            "question": "This act speaks .................................... his generosity.",
            "description": "Speak of can mean indicate or suggest.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b13b1bf35529424fbcb34991addd87e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should learn to speak ................................. your opinion.",
            "description": "To speak out your opinion is to assert it.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ac4ec22d99504f27871be0c7035eb050"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her songs really speak ................................. me.",
            "description": "If something speaks to you, it resonates with you.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d0cd6587f9454e8095276547b57bdc2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please speak .................................. I can't hear you properly.",
            "description": "To speak up is to talk more loudly.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab52961fcbdb433096863099852fe877"
        },
        {
            "question": "No one speaks ..................................... for the oppressed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bccc9c7da5b94c53ac5a77608a9f73bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I found his behavior unacceptable but I didn’t dare to speak ……………………….. about it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "58aa956f0d5b4118adfd1517a5f81ccc"
        },
        {
            "question": "If this happens again, you have to speak ………………………… him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "66fbc9ce3f7746c785a6fbde9db5b577"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last few months have been very dry – no rain to speak …………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9dd50a1563394b7baef6b30379a748dd"
        }
    ]
}